
Essential Audio Player JS
Version History

v1.0.3
released August 9, 2021
- JavaScript: init function added for manual initialization

v1.0.2
released March 8, 2021
- JavaScript: improved buffering behavior
- CSS: minor code change (button border-radius set to 50% instead of pixel value)

v1.0.1
released November 27, 2020
- JavaScript: increased button refresh frequency for smoother movement
- CSS: improved button SVG encoding (quotes)

v1.0
released July 24, 2020

Essential Audio Player Website:
https://essential.audio

