
Essential Audio Player JS
Version History

v2.0
released March 25, 2024
- JavaScript: redesigned file handling – both simplified and stabilized
- HTML: new multiple file handling in data-url attribute: now as comma-separated URLs
- JavaScript: improved click & drag behavior
- JavaScript: passive event listeners now optional (depending on the preferred scroll behavior)
- JavaScript: deprecated event property replaced by event listener
- JavaScript: Unhandled Promise Rejection issue resolved
- CSS: minor Code change (click & track sensor)

v1.0.4
released November 22, 2023
- JavaScript: init method refined to prevent a rare initialization error

v1.0.3
released August 9, 2021
- JavaScript: init method added for manual initialization

v1.0.2
released March 8, 2021
- JavaScript: improved buffering behavior
- CSS: minor code change (button border-radius set to 50% instead of pixel value)

v1.0.1
released November 27, 2020
- JavaScript: increased button refresh frequency for smoother movement
- CSS: improved button SVG encoding (quotes)

v1.0
released July 24, 2020

Essential Audio Player Website:
https://essential-audio-player.net

